Guide to the Syria Collection of photographs AD.MC.036
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Studio Series III (Box 8)
  - A studio portrait of a woman., Circa 1950-1970; ref1053; Photo Michel, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.7 x 8.5 cm (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Women; Furnishings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Damascus, Syria
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1951; ref1054; Photo Katchadour, Damascus, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 x 6.2 cm (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Boys; Children; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a man and a woman., Circa 1950-1970; ref1055; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.9 x 8.9 cm (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Damascus, Syria; Men; Women; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of five boys, a woman, and a man., 9 September 1951; ref1056; Photo Nofal, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.7 x 8.1 cm (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Men; Women; Children; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; French Writing; Syria
  - A group portrait of two girls wearing veils and a boy., Circa 1955-1970; ref1057; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.9 x 8.7 cm (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Syria; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Head Covers/Veils; Flags; Boys; Girls; Children
  - A studio portrait of a child., Circa 1955-1970; ref1058; Studio Dikran, Damascus, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 13.4 x 8.3 cm (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Children; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a baby wearing a cross., 3 March 1967; ref1059; Studio Echbelia, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 14 x 8.9 cm (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Children; Religion; Religious Crosses; Art; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Damascus, Syria
  - A portrait of a girl wearing a veil and holding a Bible., Circa 1955-1970; ref1060; Photo V. Derounian, Aleppo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.5 x 8.5 cm (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Aleppo, Syria; Head Covers/Veils; Books; Studio Photography; Furnishings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Girls; Children
  - A group portrait of a girl dressed as an angel and a girl wearing a veil., Circa 1955-1970; ref1061; Photo Ardo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.5 x 8.5 cm (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Girls; Head Covers/Veils; Costumes; Religion; Religious Crosses; Children; Furnishings; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A portrait of a girl., Circa 1950-1970; ref1062; Studio Elias Hichmé, Bab-Touma, Damas, (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 16.8 x 11.7 cm (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Damascus, Syria; Girls; Children; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of two women and two children., Circa 1950-1970; ref1063; Studio Elias Hichmé, Bab-Touma, Damas, (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 17.9 x 12.9 cm (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Women; Children; Girls; Balloons; Damascus, Syria; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of several men, women, and children at a party., Circa 1950-1970; ref1064; Studio Elias Hichmé, Bab-Touma, Damas, (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 17.8 x 12.9 cm (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Men; Women; Children; Boys; Girls; Birthdays; Events/Occasions; Food; Balloons; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A portrait of a girl., Circa 1950-1970; ref1065; Studio Elias Hichmé, Bab-Touma, Damas, (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 18.2 x 13 cm (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Girls; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Damascus, Syria; Children
  - A group portrait of a priest and a monk giving Communion to three boys (linked ref1067)., Circa 1950-1970; ref1066; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 21.7 x 16.3 cm (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Men; Priests/Clergymen; Boys; Children; Religion; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Syria
  - A group portrait of a priest and a monk giving Communion to three boys (linked ref1066)., Circa 1950-1970; ref1067; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 23.4 x 17.7 cm (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Men; Boys; Religion; Priests/Clergymen; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Syria
  - A group portrait of several men and women., 15 October 1959; ref1068; Photo Azad, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 24 x 18 cm (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Damascus, Syria; Women; Men; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of several men and three women in front of a chalk board., Circa 1950-1970; ref1069; Studio Elias Hichmé, Bab-Touma, Damas, (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 24 x 18 cm (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Men; Women; Schools/Education; Mathematics; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Damascus, Syria
  - A portrait of a woman in a costume (linked ref1071, 1072, 1073, 1074, 1075)., Circa 1950-1980; ref1070; Photo Khayam, Aleppo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 24.3 x 18 cm (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Aleppo, Syria; Women; Costumes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A portrait of a woman in a costume (linked ref1070, 1072, 1073, 1074, 1075)., Circa 1950-1980; ref1071; Photo Khayam, Aleppo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 24.3 x 18 cm (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Women; Aleppo, Syria; Costumes; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A portrait of a woman in a costume (linked ref1070, 1071, 1073, 1074, 1075)., Circa 1950-1980; ref1072; Photo Khayam, Aleppo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 24.3 x 18 cm (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Aleppo, Syria; Women; Costumes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints
  - A portrait of a woman in a costume (linked ref1070, 1071, 1072, 1074, 1075)., Circa 1950-1980; ref1073; Photo Khayam, Aleppo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 24.3 x 18 cm (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - A portrait of a woman in a costume (linked ref1070, 1071, 1072, 1073, 1075)., Circa 1950-1980; ref1074; Photo Khayam, Aleppo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 24.3 x 18 cm (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - A portrait of a woman in a costume (linked ref1070, 1071, 1072, 1073, 1074)., Circa 1950-1980; ref1075; Photo Khayam, Aleppo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 24.3 x 18 cm (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Wedding Portrait Series (Box 6)
  - A studio portrait of a couple in their wedding outfits., December 23 1962; ref1277; Tirage Photo Dadour, Alep (Aleppo, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 23.5 x 17.5 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Armenian Writing; Aleppo, Syria; Jewelry; Head Covers/Veils; Weddings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Studio Photography; Men; Women
  - A studio portrait of a couple in their wedding outfits., 1963; ref1278; Tirage Photo Dadour, Alep (Aleppo, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 23.5 x 17.5 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Aleppo, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Weddings; Head Covers/Veils; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Men; Women; English Writing
  - A studio portrait of a couple in their wedding outfits., Circa 1960-1970; ref1279; Photo Kevork, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 18.5 x 13.8 cm (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Weddings; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Studio Photography; Men; Women; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Head Covers/Veils
  - A studio portrait of a couple in their wedding outfits., Circa 1960-1970; ref1280; Photo Kevork, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 18.5 x 13.8 cm (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Studio Photography; Men; Women; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Head Covers/Veils; Weddings
  - A studio portrait of a couple in their wedding outfits., Circa 1960-1970; ref1281; Photo Kevork, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 18.5 x 13.8 cm (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Men; Women; Weddings; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Studio Photography; Head Covers/Veils; Syria